John Hazel Collection 086
People's Archive, MLK Library
John Hazel Collection
1972-1994
People's Archive, MLK Library
Hazel, John
086
0.25 Linear feet
1 Boxes
Arrangement
Processed without series.
Custodial History
Jacqueline B. Hazel, wife of John Hazel, donated the materials in this collection to the DC Public Library in November 1994.
Related Materials
Collection #040: District of Columbia Public Library Records
Scope and Contents
This collection primarily contains reproductions collected by John Hazel. The original material in this collection consists of clippings, photographs, and legal documents.
Labor unions; Libraries; Politics and government; Legal documents; Ephemera; Photographs
- Series 1
  - Awards, 1975-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Council Statement, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Party - Affirmative Action Plan, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Party - Delegate Selection Plan, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Party - Democratic Central Committee By-Laws, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Democratic Party - DC Delegate Challenge, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - King Mural Dedication, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Obituary, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)